Father , I want to confess .
What have you done ?
Nothing , father . I haven 't sinned
but I intend to commit all the evil I can .
What ?
- Why ? - Because it 's necessary .
What do you mean ? I don 't understand .
I 've discovered it .
I 've deciphered the code .
Listen to me .
I 'm speaking as a friend . Why do you keep at it ?
We 've been trying for years .
We both know it is
impossible .
You 'll only harm yourself .
Now , will you listen to me ?
Have you told anyone else ?
- Will you help me ? - Yes .
We don 't have much time .
Remember one thing .
Our enemy is powerful . He will do away with us
if he gets the chance .
He may have heard this conversation .
Holy God !
Father ...
Can we bear this cross ?
Yes .
If we stay united , we 'll manage it .
With God 's help .
EUROPE 'S GATEWAY
Give me a few coins , father . It 's for the child .
I hope you rot in Hell !
THE DAY OF THE BEAST
TRAMP BURNED alive while HE WAS sleeping
His body was removed last night
by the Police .
This vandalism
with the slogan " Clean up Madrid "
is rampant at present . in the capital .
If you want to know what your future will be , call me .
Taxi ! Taxi !
Happy are the merciful
for they shall have mercy shown them .
Happy are the pure in heart , for they shall see God .
Happy are the peacemakers , for they shall see God .
THE FUTURE is in YOUR HANDS . New Athenaeum Lecture Hall
- Why did you give me this ? - To read it , of course .
Who sent you ?
The agency .
Give me a break . Throw it away , if you want .
- Let me do my job . - You know who I am , don 't you ?
What is this ?
is it " Candid Camera " ?
I 'm in no mood for cameras .
- l want to be one of you . - You want to hand out leaflets ?
I want to see the Devil .
I don 't give a fuck what you want to see !
Go away , you 're scaring people !
I always get stuck with the crazies !
Fuck it , anyway !
What is this ?
You want to pay for one and take four ?
Don 't fucking come back !
Shit ! Another glass case .
- Good evening . - Good evening .
I 'm looking for this .
Heavy stuff .
Look in that drawer .
- You 're a priest , right ? - Yes .
In that gear ...
Well , I 'm really a theology professor .
That 's Catechism , isn 't it ? I studied Ethics , you know .
And look where l ended up !
May I hear this one ?
Heavy , right ?
It isn 't bad .
- Can you play it backwards ? - Yeah , sure .
It 'll sound the same , but it fucks up the turntable .
No , no , no , it isn 't that .
What are you looking for ?
I 'm looking for a message , a signal .
Listen to this .
They 're not famous but they 're good .
The words are real sharp .
Lots of message .
And they 're local guys .
It 's a different sound .
Well , it 's a demo .
Wait till they make a record .
Here , take it .
I won 't pay .
No problem .
Really ?
On the house . I like your taste .
A pleasure meeting you .
Going on a trip ?
- Actually , I 've just arrived . - Tomorrow , you can
see them in Hell .
Where ?
In Hell. it 's a music venue . Great name .
lmpossible to forget .
But tomorrow 's Christmas Eve . I doubt if I can go .
If you need a hostel , I know one .
I 'll write down the name . My old lady runs it .
A nice friendly atmosphere .
Here , call round .
Thank you .
So long .
SATANNlCA ln Concert
Garcia 's Boarding House .
Good evening .
- Who is on the line ? - This is Mari Carmen .
Where are you calling from ?
- From Valladolid . And what do you want to know ?
My husband is unemployed . Will it take him very long
to find work ?
Let 's see , Mari Carmen .
Mari Carmen , your husband isn 't going to find work
for a long period of time . At least five years .
- But there 's something else . - What ?
A serious health problem .
- For my husband ? - No , for you .
I 'd like a room .
The only one left is being done up .
I 'm not fussy .
I can 't accept anyone at this time .
The boy didn 't tell me about that .
What boy ?
One who works in a record shop .
Come in .
The room costs 3,000 . The bath tap doesn 't work .
No visitors or pets allowed , and I 'll need some l.D.
Thank you .
The front door key .
And I 'll always be here to open this door .
Thank you .
Can you hear me ?
Yes , yes .
I think you should get ready for the worst .
- Are you staying a week ? - No , just tonight .
This is too much .
It doesn 't matter .
This is the room. I told you it was being done up .
It 's perfect . Thank you .
- Need anything ? - No , not just now .
All right . Happy Christmas .
I 've told you before .
You accept nobody at night !
- You open the door , that 's all . - lt was a priest .
Even if it was the Pope !
You can 't trust anybody .
They pull a knife and that 's it .
The world is full of bastards ! The woman on the second floor
was robbed on the stairs by a guy with a syringe .
She got off lightly .
Look at what this street is like at night time .
Full of whores , blacks , drug addicts , killers .
It 's disgusting !
You know what ?
I wish that one of them would come here .
First , I 'd blow his balls off with a shotgun !
For being a coward !
Then I 'd break his bones .
He 'd be in a wheelchair the rest of his life !
He 'd know what suffering was !
He 's really a priest ?
He wore a soutane .
And so ?
Look , your son sent him . And this is Christmas Eve .
If he 's a friend of my son , that 's even worse !
He paid 25,000 pesetas for one night !
That 's different .
He probably taught my son at the Jesuits .
I don 't know .
I still don 't like what you did .
- l 'll speak to him . - He seems very nice .
OCCULTSClENCES
Demon Magic
" l can help you achieve the impossible . " Cavan .
You have to pay for the book .
What ? What book ?
Name ?
Angel .
- Angel what ? - Angel Berriartua .
- Are you a priest ? - Yes .
Priest . That 's great .
" The Magic World of Professor Cavan . "
Aren 't you a bit old to be stealing books ?
I need that book .
I need lots of things too
but I work all day to pay for them .
I can 't buy it .
- You can 't ? - No .
Why can 't you ?
You have no money ?
- No , it isn 't that . - So what is it ?
I must learn to do evil .
Why is that ?
I have to contact Satan .
Satan ?
That can 't be easy .
No , that 's why I need the book .
I 'm a theology professor .
I 've studied the Apocalypse of St. John for 25 years
and I 've discovered that it is just a cryptogram .
- A kleptogram ? - No , a cryptogram .
It 's a message in code .
A secret message hidden behind the words .
- And you 've discovered it ? - Exactly .
Last week .
I based my work on a numerical transcription of the Apocalypse .
At first , I used Tritheim 's Steganography . Have you read
Tritheim ?
Tritheim ? I think not .
Well , it 's fundamental .
It inspired me to see the Apocalypse
not as an allegory but as an equation .
Each letter has its own number . So , for example
Daleth is worth four , and Synn
is worth three hundred , so we can ...
- Excuse me . - What is it ?
Could you come up to the toy department ?
I 'm busy now . I 'll come up later .
We can do this with all the words and ...
Father , does anyone else know this ?
Yes , of course . But he died .
- Two days ago . - l 'm sorry .
Don 't worry , I believe you . We can sort everything out .
But what does the message say ?
The message is a figure , a date .
The date of the end of the world .
Today , to be exact .
Yes , that is very important .
Just wait here for a moment , please .
One second .
Check the asylums to see
if a priest has escaped .
And tell them to send someone .
Well , father ...
Mr. Cerezo !
Are you all right ?
Look , this is all burned . Totally burned .
Hey , father !
- ls your room all right ? - Yes , it 's fine .
I must talk to you
Jose Maria .
If there 's any problem , I 'll get them to change you .
Jose Maria ...
Hot stuff. I 've been trying for a year to shag her .
- But it 's no go . - What ?
Shag her . Know what I mean ?
It was no go . She 's from a village in Toledo .
I hear you 're in the new room . I 'm Rosario , Jose Maria 's mother .
A pleasure .
Will you have some rabbit ?
No , I have to talk to Jose Maria .
We 've got lots .
He 's working now
in a record shop , but he 's really an artist .
Fuck off !
He 's doing a drawing course just now .
But as the shop won 't give him a contract ...
Enjoy your meal .
I bet you that we 'll have rabbit again tonight .
She always buys the fucking special offers !
May I ask you a favor ?
Sure , anything .
Grandad !
This is my grandad .
He likes going around the house starkers .
This is a friend , Father ...
Angel Berriartua .
I love him .
This is just
to jazz him up a bit , because he 's pretty old now .
Grandad ...
That 's it .
They say it 's bad circulation .
The other day he said he saw the Virgin .
He 's too much . Want some acid ?
No , thank you .
If it weren 't for me , my fucking mother
would put him away .
Jose Maria , I have a mission .
Where ? In Africa ?
No , I have a mission to carry out .
Something I have to do here in the city .
- You 're a Satannic follower ? - Yeah , sure .
Can you invoke the devil ?
- l have to invoke the devil . - Why ?
Because of the Apocalypse .
- The film ? - No , no .
The book in the Bible .
Never mind .
Tonight , the Antichrist will be born , but I don 't know where .
- So I must invoke the Devil . - Heavy !
I 'm a sinner now .
I 've betrayed Christ to make salvation possible .
I 'm one hell of a sinner too .
I must sell my soul to the devil but I don 't know how .
I stole a book , but it 's no good .
It doesn 't explain it very well .
It 's Cavan , from the TV !
My mother loves him . He 's a bastard .
There isn 't much time . Can we do anything ?
Cool it , we 'll manage it .
THE DARKZONE
Here he is , the investigator of the occult
the magician of mystery
the master
of the supernatural .
The man who knows the present
the past and the future .
The internationally known Professor
Cavan .
Tonight 's program is going to be very special .
We 're not going to talk about UFOs or miracle cures .
Nor will we be taking your calls .
Tonight we have with us a guest who is
exceptional .
Someone about whom we have all heard
but only a few really know .
I am talking about the Devil !
Heavy !
How do you feel now it 's over ?
Great , thanks to you and the Dark Zone team .
Juan Carlos Cruz is eleven years old .
A month ago , Juan Carlos had a strange illness
which no doctor could diagnose .
Juan Carlos behaved as if he were someone else .
As he said , " Like I had a man inside " .
The Dark Zone team got a call from his desperate parents
unable to find any reason for their son 's behavior .
Soon after , we went to their home .
This is what happened .
It 's you ! At last , you 're here !
- Where is he ? - ln his room .
Take it easy , ma 'am .
Whatever happens in there
remember it 's for your son 's good .
Let 's go !
This way !
What a fucking set-up !
Here ! The boy is in here !
Hold him down !
Quickly !
Our Father , who art in ...
That 's the man I need .
That 's for sure .
I have to talk to him . Come on .
Wait till the program 's over .
I exorcise you by the blood of Christ
and return you to your lair !
Our Father
who art in Heaven
hallowed be Thy name .
Thy kingdom come .
Juan Carlos ...
Juan Carlos , how are you ? Are you all right ?
What happened ?
Heavy !
That 's him .
Yes , that 's Cavan , the creep .
Let 's go !
Last week 's program was real heavy .
- Hurry , we 're losing him . - Cool it .
I 've got him . It was about a chick
who was raped by aliens . Did you see it ?
If you 'd seen her ! She looked like a real slut .
I bet you anything she provoked them .
I don 't have a television .
You don 't ? What do you do at night ?
Pray .
Pray ? But you must have seen programs like
" Final Questions " or " Sister Citroen " .
No , that was the first program I 've ever seen .
Fuck !
Stop ! Stop !
He didn 't indicate !
Clean up Madrid
I 'll leave the money here .
There he is !
Didn 't you see " Jesus Christ Superstar " ?
It was fucking great . " Hosanna , hey
sanna , sanna sanna hey , sanna hey , sanna ! "
Or the other one that went , " Jesus Christ , Superstar ! "
- Stop ! He 's parking ! - All right .
Here , father , it 'll bring you luck .
Ennio ! This is Susana !
I 'm on my way over . We can have dinner together .
But remember , tomorrow we 're taking my mother to lunch .
See you in a little while . So long . See you soon .
Good evening . You must listen ...
Who are you ?
I am Angel Berriartua , from the University ...
Who gave you this address ? This is my home .
Yes. I 'm from the University of Deusto ...
Please , call the program for an appointment .
Or write a letter .
But we can 't talk now . Good-bye .
But I 've discovered something incredible !
That 's great , but this isn 't the time .
Call me tomorrow . I 'll deal with it personally .
No , it has to be tonight !
Why can 't it be tomorrow ?
The Antichrist is coming !
All right , let 's see .
Leave me your address .
I 'll call you tomorrow morning
you come to the program and we 'll discuss
the Antichrist . All right ?
Wait , I 'll get my diary .
Now , your name was ... ?
My God ! What have you done ? Are you crazy ?
I 'm just desperate .
Now you 'll listen to me
carefully .
Have you read Tritheim ?
Pope John Paul ll receives Spanish theologians
Heavy , man !
- You can 't park here . Move on . - What ?
- Move on . - Am I in the way ?
- You 're badly parked . - My pal 's coming now .
- ls this your car ? - No , it 's my mother 's .
Your papers , please .
It 's always the same fucking story !
You see ?
Metraton can even substitute Shaddai . But unfortunately
this system only works with single words !
That 's a shame .
There had to be something
that had confused thinkers over the years. lsn 't that so ?
What ? Yes , yes . Please , continue .
Well , I found what it was !
All the Christian cabbalists were trying to find a message .
A word behind the Apocalypse .
The Word of God .
They were wrong .
The message isn 't a word . It 's a number .
A number !
The sum of the value of all the words in the text .
Two million
one hundred and twenty six thousand , four hundred and ten .
That number is a date .
2,126,410 days in the Jewish calendar of the time .
Understand ?
A date , a specific day in the calendar !
Yes , a day .
Yes . The Day of the Beast .
The Jews counted time
from the beginning of the world
which they dated 3,761 years before the birth of Christ .
Given that they used a lunar calendar
and we use a solar one
that is equivalent to December 25 , 1995 .
You mean , tomorrow .
No ! Tonight , before dawn . What is the Apocalypse about ?
I don 't know , I can 't remember .
The beginning of the end of the world .
If we don 't prevent it
the Antichrist will be born tonight .
But I need your help .
You must help me contact the Devil .
What ?
I know the date , but not the place !
Where will it be ?
I don 't know . I haven 't the slightest idea .
To find out , I have to join them .
I must sell my soul to the Devil .
I 'll be at the ceremony tonight and I 'll kill him there .
I 'll kill the Antichrist
and the world may be saved .
That 's why I need to contact the Devil , and you can do it .
But this is all ... This can 't be happening !
Will you be much longer ?
I 'm badly parked again and we 'll have to move soon .
You 're the TV guy ?
- A pleasure . - Who is this ?
I 'm Jose Mari .
Neat place !
These masks are plastic , aren 't they ?
If you want to rob the house , go ahead
but there 's no money .
How can I make you believe me ?
All right. lf you want me to believe you , I do .
But why is it going to be here ? It could be somewhere else !
No ! It will be here , in Madrid !
You don 't believe me . There are hundreds of signs !
Look .
Newly born babies are disappearing . Just look !
Fifty cases !
Desecrated graves .
100 cases here in Madrid in just one year !
is that not enough ?
It just proves you 're crazy !
And if it is true , how will you fool the Devil ?
Will you turn up like it 's a wedding ?
No , it won 't be like a wedding .
There won 't be thousands adoring him . Nothing like that !
- Oh , no ? - No !
Damn !
The Devil tries to imitate God in order mock him .
The birth of his son will imitate the birth of Jesus .
Like a secret , but visible to all
as in Bethlehem .
Will the Wise Men be there too ?
- We 'll be the Wise Men . - Us ? Fucking great !
And is that asshole going as the pageboy ?
I don 't like
your attitude .
Listen carefully. I am sacrificing eternal life
to fool the Devil
and to kill the Antichrist !
Great ! Kidnapped by a saint !
Quite the opposite .
I 'll take every chance to commit evil .
The Devil will trust me .
The first thing
is to draw
the pentacle .
It 's in the middle pages .
A circle with symbols .
You must draw it on the floor , and then we stand inside it .
- So the Devil can 't pass it . - That 's right .
What else ?
Be patient ! There are lots of things to remember !
Calm down . You know what 's vital .
A sword .
A sacred sword , or a large knife . It 's like a magic wand .
There 'll be one in the kitchen .
What else ?
An Amanita muscaria .
A mushroom ? What for ? Are you trying to fool me ?
No , mushrooms are psychotropics . You know , like drugs .
Yeah , I 've tried those . It 's like a kind of acid
like LSD .
I have some here .
It isn 't for me , father .
Some pals of mine are having a party .
Got the lucky gloves ?
Yeah , this is it .
Will it do ?
This is absurd !
Don 't you see that this is just a farce for assholes ?
Assholes who watch my program and buy my book !
- That 's the truth ! - Are we back to that ?
You think that I enjoy this ?
That I like using violence ?
I have no other choice . It 's the only solution .
You should collaborate .
We need
a goblet , with four consecrated hosts
anointed with a maiden 's blood .
Got any maiden 's blood ?
- That isn 't in the book . - l know .
Not everything is . That 's why you need me .
Look , without the maiden 's blood
the invocation will be of no use !
I think it 's time to forget it !
Excuse me .
I 've made a mistake .
Susana ! Run !
Get away ! He 's crazy !
Darling !
What are you doing ?
What happened ?
- She fell down the stairs . - My God !
It should have been deliberate but it was an accident .
Christ ! What a dame , father ! How did you do it ?
I could only find sliced bread
but I cut some of the symbols on it .
Good , thank you .
You do the pentacle . To what ?
- You said we needed some blood . - Wait a minute !
Now what is it ?
- She 's no use . - Why is she no use ?
She 's no use . She isn 't a maiden .
She isn 't a virgin . Her blood is no use .
Sure she isn 't a virgin ?
Absolutely. I swear it .
And you need a virgin 's blood .
Otherwise , it 's no good , I told you .
You 're right .
Jose Maria , finish the pentacle . I 'll be out for an hour .
- Where are you going ? - To find some blood .
You think you can find a virgin in one hour ?
Yes .
With God 's help .
" Christmas Eve is coming , Christmas Eve is going .
We are going too and we won 't be back again . "
You 're soaked !
It 's raining .
- Will I fix you something hot ? - No , no , no .
Well , yes . A coffee .
" The Virgin is combing her hair
in amongst the veils ... "
- Are you alone ? - No way !
Madam is asleep , nothing will waken her .
So I have to prepare everything .
- ls there a celebration ? - Christmas Eve .
Of course , Christmas Eve ! What was I thinking of ?
- Won 't you have something ? - No , I won 't .
You could have some tea , or camomile .
I just had some , and anyway , I have to fix the salad .
I won 't insist if that 's how it is .
All right then , I will .
Are you staying for dinner ? We have some lovely rabbit .
Rabbit ? That 's nice !
But I can 't , I 'm in a hurry . I have to go out again .
- May I ask you a question ? - What is it ?
Are you a virgin ?
- What ? - Are you a virgin ?
Don 't worry , I 'm a priest .
I 'm asking like I was your father or mother .
No , no , I don 't mind . It 's just that
I wasn 't expecting it .
You took me by surprise .
- You don 't have to answer . - l don 't mind !
- Mmm ... - What ?
Yes , I am .
Until I get married
nothing doing .
That 's very good , child .
Was Madam behind this ?
- lf she thinks her son and I ... - No , I just wondered .
He 's never touched me !
He 's a drug addict , he 's a pig , and he 's fat !
I don 't know what to do .
Don 't worry. I 'll talk to him . He won 't bother you again .
- Really ? - Yes. I 'm here to help others .
Have your coffee .
- l don 't feel like it . - Have it at once !
I 'm a bit edgy .
I get edgy and ...
- l 'm very edgy , that 's all . - l can see that . What 's wrong ?
- lt 's very serious . - What is ?
I can 't explain it all now , there isn 't time .
- l need your blood . - What ?
Not all of it . Just a little bottle .
Why do you want my blood ? For a transfusion ?
No , for an invocation . I have to invoke the devil .
This will sound odd
but we had a girl who wasn 't a virgin
and as it seems we must have a virgin
I thought of you .
No , I don 't want to . I don 't like the idea , really .
Look , you needn 't worry .
It 's a real emergency .
Keep away !
Now , don 't be like that . It 'll only take a moment .
Look , we can do it with this and no one will ever know .
- l 'll stick this in you ! - Look ...
Mina !
Where are you ?
Mina ! That girl !
Yes ?
- ls Tere there ? - What ?
- ls that the whore house ? - No , it isn 't .
You 've made a mistake .
You want the house opposite .
The whores are over there ! People come here to sleep !
I 'll call the police .
Mina ! Where are you ?
Mina ! Are you asleep ?
Where the hell are you ?
Mina ! is that you ?
No , it 's me .
Excuse me , father .
I can 't find Mina .
Do you know where she is ?
I 've been in here for ages , I 've seen nothing .
Are you ill ?
No , I 'm perfectly well , thank you .
Why is the light off ?
The light !
That 's much better .
Don 't worry about me .
It was the rabbit ...
- Police ? - This is police headquarters .
- There 's a murderer in my house . - Name , address and l.D. number ?
What ? What did you say ?
Give me your name , address and l.D. number .
Hello ? Hello ?
Murderer !
What are you doing ?
You don 't have to fuck up the floor !
The book says you must do it with the magic knife .
I put that in for the sake of it .
Fuck you ! You shouldn 't have put it !
All you TV people are real fuckers !
You 're always laughing at people !
- You 're in real trouble . - Who , me ?
Yes , you .
Why ?
This is a kidnapping , and that woman
may be dead .
You could go down for a few years .
You 're aiding a psychopath , a dangerous madman !
Who knows what he 's up to now ?
All I 'm doing is drawing something .
But you 're helping him . You 're helping
a murderer .
Listen to me !
Can you hear me ? Untie me !
Lunatic !
Do you want money ?
- Say something ! - That 'll be the cops again .
Damn the bastard !
Fuck it !
That fucking tow truck ! For Chrissake !
- What 's up ? - l 'm sorry .
- Where 's my car ? - We waited for ages .
Then we called the tow truck .
Some friends are expecting us at a party and ...
Susana !
What 's going on ?
Untie me ! Hurry !
He 's coming back !
- What happened ? - Untie me ! Get the knife !
Hurry !
Are you in trouble ?
Come on , hurry up !
- What are you doing ? - Calling the police !
There 's no time . Get the fucking knife !
Sorry !
Good evening !
Now , don 't panic !
Careful !
He 's coming ! Hurry up !
Forget about that ! Hide !
She 's gone . She went to call the police !
Get out , Susana !
Run , Susana !
I brought this .
Will it help ?
A tape ? What 's it for ?
You know , demonic music .
Heavy ? You want to play heavy ?
It 's Death Metal . It isn 't the same .
Sattanica . They 're very good .
- Right . - lt 's a form of invocation .
Some have to be played backwards .
Look , do whatever you want . Listen to it backwards .
Play heavy if you want , but I 'd rather you didn 't .
You 're the expert .
Thank you . is everything ready ?
Knife , bread , LSD , immaculate blood .
In under an hour !
Let 's get started , please . And in silence .
Read this .
Out loud . It 's your pact with the Devil .
" My lord and master Satan
I recognize you as my God and promise to serve you .
I now renounce Jesus Christ .
I promise to adore you every day
to do all the evil I can
and to draw as many as I can to do evil .
I surrender to you my body , my soul and my life
dedicated to you for ever
with no intention of repentance . "
That 's it .
- Now , sign it with your blood . - Heavy !
And now ?
Burn it .
Now what ?
Nothing . That 's all .
What did you expect ? Are you convinced ?
- Nothing 's happening . - Of course not .
This is just messing around .
I told you . The Devil !
It 's incredible !
Be quiet !
Will we try the music ?
No , we won 't . We 're going to wait .
Christ !
You see ? It was scared off !
It couldn 't cross the pentacle !
My God !
Have they gone ? What happened ?
Nothing , it 's all right .
- lt 's better if you go home . - What ? And leave you here ?
Go home and I 'll call you later .
They almost killed us , and you want to stay here !
What 's wrong with you ?
I 'm perfectly all right . Nothing happened .
Now , come on . Let 's go .
Don 't worry , I 'll call you tomorrow .
Nothing 's wrong . We 'll talk tomorrow .
There are hundreds of combinations .
Thousands of millions . There are 15 letters .
A permutation of 15 elements with three repeated twice
and two , three times , giving us a total of
4,540,536,000 possibilities .
My head 's spinning. I think none of them makes sense .
- Almost none . - We use all the letters ?
- Yes . - That 's it .
This is not a game .
Holy God !
Don 't answer .
It might be Susana .
It isn 't Susana .
I can 't help it !
- ls there another way out ? - No .
We must get out of here !
Come on !
Follow me ! Don 't just sit there !
Come on ! Hurry !
- lt 's him . He 's come for us ! - The window !
This way .
We 're going to die !
- Stop laughing ! - This is very high !
Don 't push . We have to hold on to the bars .
- Hurry ! - Don 't push me ! I 'll fall !
Don 't look down !
Be careful !
Take it slowly .
We 're at the top .
Only six more letters !
- Just as well ! - Wait for me !
Cool it , father .
We 'll wait for you .
Don 't crowd me !
What are you doing ?
- Be careful ! - Cool it , man .
Fuck , this is high !
Look up here , folks !
Be careful , you fool !
I can 't stop !
I can 't stop ! We 're so high up !
- Don 't look down ! - Look !
Shut up !
You 'll knock us off !
Hey , cool it , man .
Going down !
I 'm going to kill myself !
Fucking great !
Let go of me !
- Let go ! - Climb up !
Now , be careful . We 're going to move down bit by bit .
- He isn 't thinking straight . - Am I not ?
What if I jump off right now ?
Stop talking rubbish !
We 'll all be fucked !
We 're going down ! We 're going down !
Look , father ! Look , I 'm flying !
Like the angels !
My God !
Don 't let go of me !
Santa Claus !
Santa Claus is in the house !
Mom ! Dad ! Come here !
Santa Claus has come in through the window !
Are you ready , love ?
Let 's see Santa Claus .
- Happy Christmas . - Good-bye .
And so ended the attempted kidnapping
of Ennio Lombardi
better known as Professor Cavan
from " The Dark Zone "
shown on this station .
The motive for the kidnapping is unknown
and those responsible , as yet unidentified ...
I 've just heard the news !
I rang the hospital but you 'd gone !
How are you ? Will I get you a chair ?
- Do they know where they are ? - We have no idea !
Just as well .
You should be in hospital . How are you ?
Leave me be ! I want to talk to the TVguy !
- Why ? - We 're on in two hours .
- What ? - A special program .
And we stop the Christmas programs ?
I think you must be in shock !
That is absolutely impossible !
What you asked for ...
This ? This is garbage ! Shit !
It 's all they could find in Madrid !
There must be more !
Have you checked the program on sects ?
That 's true ! What about the sects ?
Very well .
If that 's all there is , you 're fired .
It would be easier if we knew what we were looking for .
Don 't you fucking listen ?
I told you !
A place , a fucking site !
I don 't know .
A building , a square , gardens .
The place where Satanists meet here in Madrid !
But don 't bring me another boy possessed by the Devil !
But we only had an hour . We didn 't even have any dinner .
We need time .
If I don 't get it by tonight , you can shove your dinner !
Ennio , wait !
We can 't wait .
- Calm down ! - We can 't wait !
Mr. Cavan , your autograph ?
is someone going to clean this , or do you expect me to do it ?
Ennio ! Ennio !
Mr. Cavan ...
Can you leave that for later ? We 're trying to work .
- How are you ? - What the fuck are you doing ?
Excuse me , happy Christmas .
Can 't you see we 're busy ?
I 'm glad that you 're better . Will you sign your book for me ?
My wife and kids love your program .
This book is shit . A fraud . Tell your wife and kids that .
- Fuck ! - What ?
- l 've lost my pen . - Use this .
You 're a genius !
We 'll slay them tonight !
Everyone else has carols and we have the Devil !
We 'll have to do a re-run .
- Your wife 's name ? - Mari-Angeles .
Dump the program .
What ?
Forget the program !
Are you crazy ? Why have you sent everyone to look for
the Devil 's temple ?
The Antichrist will be born tonight .
What ?
Shut up . Here you are .
Thank you .
I got a fright when I saw you on the News , climbing ...
Why don 't you fuck off ?
Wait a minute ! The book ...
Thank you .
What is it , Cavan ? Aren 't we paying you enough ?
Do you want to be fired and go to another channel ?
Are you trying to annoy me so we 'll throw you out ?
You hurt my eye !
What are you looking at ?
In all the time
we 've worked together , you 've never listened to me !
You know that ?
Keep moving .
Keep moving , don 't stop . Keep moving .
We 're stuck . The cops are all over .
Time is running out . It 'll be dawn in a few hours .
We won 't last five minutes out there .
What will we do ?
We must be very close by now . If only there was a ...
What ? What do you want ?
A sign . We need a sign .
Fuck !
NEWATHENAEUM
Have science and technology left it meaningless ?
The answer is no .
The First World War
Hitler 's rise to power
or Russia 's conversion
are pure facts .
Proof of the clairvoyant power of Michel de Nostradamus
the great futurologist , scorned by science
but praised by experts who studied his work .
Those who discovered ...
A neat place , father !
We can stay here until it all cools down .
The most important thing about Nostradamus was his ...
Why didn 't I realize ?
It will be here !
... thus showing us humanity 's future .
- What is humanity 's future ? - What are you doing ?
Well , that is the subject of this talk .
We shall try to analyze the work of Nostradamus
from a perspective ...
The Antichrist will be born tonight .
Let 's see .
As anyone who has studied the subject knows
Nostradamus never talks about a specific date
but about the Third World War ...
.. and when the Antipope ...
Nostradamus has nothing to do with all this .
- lf you have a question ... - Yes .
I have one .
Afterwards , please .
- lt 'll be here , won 't it ? - We 'll be thrown out .
Why not admit it ?
It 's going to be here , I know . Answer me .
After this talk we 'll have questions .
Don 't try to fool me , too .
Listen , I am one of you .
You must believe I 'm with you . I sold my soul to the Evil One .
Will you please sit down ?
Trust in me ! Trust in me !
Just sit down !
Father , come on ! Let 's go !
I signed with my blood .
We 're asking you politely . Get out !
What 's wrong ?
- Why ? What 's wrong ? - Father , let 's go !
Wait ! Listen !
Wait !
What is this ?
Attention , children .
On the junior floor of our store
you 'll find all the toys you requested for Christmas .
And the Three Wise Men are here
to get your letters . Happy Christmas !
There he is !
Excuse me , you can 't ...
Stop , you bastard ! Get in , father !
Hurry up ! Start the car ! Get us out of here , fast !
Where are we going ?
We 're losing them .
- We have to go back . - How can we ? It 's full of cops .
I must speak to him . He can 't have gone far .
That speaker ? He 's in Buenos Aires by now .
What are you looking at ?
There he is ! There he is !
- Stop the car ! - What are you talking about ?
- Be careful ! - lt 's him !
Stop the car !
Listen !
Wait !
Tell me where he 'll be born !
Where ?
What did I do ? Let me go !
Where will the birth be ?
Come on ! We haven 't got all night !
- What are you talking about ? - Come on !
Will I kill him ?
But I ... I 've never hurt anyone !
All I do is give talks ! I swear , that 's all !
Leave me alone !
Don 't hurt me , for God 's sake ! Please !
He knows nothing .
Will I let him go ?
Run , bastard !
Nostradamus ! Big mouth !
And watch what you do ! I know your face !
Asshole !
Come on , get up ! We can 't stay here !
- l 'm so tired . - We have to get a car !
- Why ? - So that we don 't get caught !
It 's no use . He 's playing with us .
Who ?
The Devil . Don 't you realize ? He 's laughing at us .
Yeah , I guess , but we still have to move .
There 's something I haven 't told you .
Tell me another day . We ...
Your mother fell down the stairs .
- What ? - Well , really , I pushed her .
She tried to kill me , when I went for the blood .
It was an accident .
- So the blood we used ... - Mina 's .
- ls she dead too ? - l only gave her some pills .
Heavy !
- So Mina was a virgin ? - Yes .
How do you know ?
She told me .
Fuck the old lady , anyway .
But what will happen
to Grandad ?
Go and see him .
Yeah , and leave you alone here .
- l can look after myself . - Sure !
Some chance !
Look , you wait here for five minutes
and I 'll come back with a car .
ATLASTHEAVEN is sending YOU THE signal YOU WERE waiting FOR .
Clean up Madrid
- You 're one of them . - What ?
I know everything .
It 'll be here . Today is the Day of the Beast .
No , Satannica are on tonight . You can check dates at the bar .
Stop shooting up !
That 's enough !
Christ !
What did they do to you ?
Shit ! The bastards ! I shouldn 't have left you .
Shit !
Come on ! Let 's go !
I said I 'd be five minutes .
Couldn 't you have waited ?
Shit !
Here .
Now what ?
His name is Angel Berriartua .
He is a theology professor at the University of Deusto .
- Hello ? - The Dark Zone .
- Hello ? - Yes ?
Get me Professor Cavan .
Tell him that the priest is here with me .
- What ? - He 's right here .
Who are you ?
Say I 'm the one who fucked up his floor .
Wait a moment .
- Yes ? Hello ? - Cavan ?
Cavan ! This is Jose Mari . Wait a minute .
Father ! It 's Cavan ! He 's alive . He 's on the TV .
He wants to talk to you . He 's been looking for you .
Come on , that 's it .
Just a bit more .
Come on , take the phone . Look , there he is .
is that you ?
I can see you in the shop .
- What are you doing ? - Trying to help .
That 's how you help ?
The best way to find you was by using the program .
Now , listen .
I 'm on to something . Where are you ?
I don 't know. ln Hell .
Please , listen to me !
I 'm with you . We have to talk !
I think I 've found it . You hear ?
- May I ask a favor ? - Whatever you want .
Call the police .
What ?
Tell them to come and get me .
What is this ?
Do you think this is a trick ? That I 'm in with the police ?
Yes , I suppose so .
Listen to what I 'm going to say .
This is a warning
for the 10 million assholes watching this fucking program !
The end of the world is tonight !
You understand ? This very night !
Christmas Eve is fucked ! Christmas is fucked !
It 's all fucked !
While you are in your homes happily watching the TV
outside on the streets
the Antichrist 's reign is beginning !
I make my living telling the future .
So now you know .
is that what you wanted ?
Are you listening ?
I 've found the place where he 's going to be born !
There is still time before dawn .
- l think I was mistaken . - How ? In the date ?
- ln everything . - How do you mean ?
This is madness .
- Maybe poor circulation . - What ?
Maybe I 'm mad .
The three of us saw that thing in my house !
You see what you want .
I don 't care if we 're mad .
Fuck ! Can you hear me ?
Listen , I 've found the mark of the Devil !
The mark of the Devil ?
He 'll be cut off !
Put in more money !
I 'm out of change .
Tell me where you are !
- Shit ! - We cut the transmission .
You 've screwed up the program !
We interrupted everything so you could find a madman !
Then you go and lose him !
You !
- What did he say ? - What ?
- When I asked where he was ? - l don 't know .
- lf it isn 't taped , you 're dead ! - He said " l don 't know " !
What else ? After that , what else ?
I don 't know. ln Hell .
What does it matter ? This is Hell !
We have a minute before we 're back on .
Sit here and calm down . Say anything .
Say it 's the end of the world , whatever you like , but say it !
Don 't destroy me , Cavan . The whole country is watching !
- l need a newspaper . - What the fuck for ?
Music Venue : Hell
Let 's go !
What 's this ?
This is all you 've got ?
- They 're photocopies . - And the signatures ?
Satan . So what ?
It 's the document we used in the invocation .
Notice anything
about the signature ?
- Marks . - Right .
Now look at the other documents . You see ?
They 're repeated .
In all the signed pacts kept since the 15th Century .
The same mark .
- l still don 't understand . - Fuck it !
One hand made the signatures through the centuries !
That proves nothing .
They were copied , that 's all .
All right .
Jose Mari , take the steering wheel !
Keep on driving .
All right , they could be copies .
Now , look at this .
He 's a boy we exorcised on the program .
The one we saw in the bar .
Do you still not understand ? It 's the mark
of the Devil ! Did the boy copy it ?
Look at the wounds !
It 's the same sign !
The Devil does it to his people with a claw .
His real signature .
Let me see .
Be careful !
What are you doing ?
Stop the car !
You still don 't see !
Listen .
- What is the sign of Christ ? - Just forget it , please .
Answer me ! What is the sign of Christ ?
- The cross . - Exactly . The cross .
The cross .
- You 're drawing it for me ? - And Christians ...
Where do they celebrate Christ 's birth ?
- ln a church . - ln a church .
In a church .
And
what is a church ?
Come on !
Answer .
What is a church ? A cross , fuck it !
An enormous three dimensional cross .
A cross with doors and windows .
You still don 't see ?
Look .
This
is the Devil 's mark .
Remember ? You said it yourself .
The Devil always tries to imitate Christ .
He 's the dark side of God !
If God 's temple is a cross
Satan 's temple
must be like this .
Well , you have it right there .
We 've found it .
You realize ?
A secret visible to all .
Just like you said ...
- We must go down ! - What for ?
They 'll come up after us !
- But we mustn 't fail now . - Come on , you have to hide !
Isn 't he on the TV ?
He 's the bastard who tells the future .
My wife loves him .
Know what ?
I foresee things too .
You doubt it ?
Listen to this .
I see that very soon
you 're going to have a health problem .
Something permanent .
But first , a carol .
" On December 25 , boom , boom , boom ! "
Get away !
Now , father ! Quickly !
Go on ! Get going !
- l think he 's laughing . - He 's a joker .
You think we 're funny ?
This is not a game .
Let 's liven things up .
Clean up Madrid
Here he is , the investigator of the occult .
He knows the present , past and future .
The internationally known Professor Cavan !
Thank you .
Today we begin a new era in " The Dark Zone " .
After a nine month break
we have returned to arise from the ashes .
We will always remember Ennio Lombardi
the former presenter , a great professional
a great friend and a brilliant communicator
who disappeared in such dramatic circumstance .
Wherever you are , my public sends you this applause .
But let us now turn to the future
in that mysterious world we explore
in " The Dark Zone " .
He 's got no style . He can 't move .
We 'll lose our audience with that idiot .
What really fucks me about this is that I can 't tell anyone .
About what ?
Fuck it ! We saved the world and nobody knows it !
They wouldn 't understand . Forget it .
A brilliant communicator !
What rubbish !
Come along .
Lean on me .